Do you remember, Felix, when you first
identified as a dead head?
>> Yeah, it was my first show. Uh, I'm a
late bloomer. My first show was 5491 at
Cal Expo in Sacramento in California,
which is where I'm from. Um, and just as
you know, the music was playing ahead of
time and then as soon as the band came
out and hit that first note and then
everybody started dancing and I wasn't
expecting that and I just felt like the
the freedom that everybody had and the
music that I had been listening [music]
to up to that point, it's like, okay,
this is where I belong. This is one of
my tribes. This [music] is this is home.
>> Did you get up and dance?
>> I did not dance. I'm dance challenged,
but that's another story for another
time. I find that kind of hard to
believe.
>> It's completely true. What about you?
When did you first know that you were a
dead head?
>> I think it was also my first show, which
was not the Grateful Dead. It was Dead
in Company. So, some of the surviving
members with other younger guys in the
mix, John Mayer. I went to see them
during their very first tour in the fall
of 2015.
And I remember I w I got there a little
bit late and I walked in and they were
already playing Feel Like a Stranger,
which is kind of a scary death song, you
know, and it was kind of fitting cuz
[music] I was like an 18-year-old in
this crowd of people and it felt like I
was walking into something that had a
really big history and I didn't
understand it yet, but I could
definitely feel it. [music] And then and
then you know then I got on the bus then
I started going to all the shows.